

# MIKAEL LE GAL

#### CONTACT

legal.mikael@gmail.com

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a creative, detail-oriented person with a passion for everything related to design and learning. My experience as a freelancer has allowed me to develop excellent problem-solving skills and the ability to work independently, but I am still a team player at heart.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2018 - 2020 Högskolan i Skövde

Master's Degree in Informatics. Composed of two Magister's programmes: Serious Games, and Digital Narrative, Games and Cultural Heritage.

#### 2011 - 2011 University of Alicante

Course in 3D modeling and animation with Blender.

#### 2006 - 2011 University of Alicante

Architectural Technologist. Bachelor's degree on construction and structure engineering specialized in the areas of Project Management, Construction Management and Patrimony Intervention.

## **SKILLS** Unitu C# Git Photoshop Illustrator Blender **ZBrush**

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 2014 - 2019 Digital Artist

Freelance extra job working as illustrator or graphic designer for several clients, producing graphical elements such as festival posters, album covers, corporate videos and more.

#### Private Tutor 2011 - 2018

Freelance job working as a private tutor in the subjects of Mathematics, Physics, Arts and English to children from 5 to 18 years old. In Alicante, San Vicente, and San Juan; Spain.

#### 2014 - 2014 Camp Counselor

Working for YMCA Hayo-Went-Ha Camp organizing activities and taking care of a small group of children at a camp and during camping trips. In Michigan, USA.

#### 2010 -2010 Private Tutor

Working for Know-How S.L. as a tutor in subjects such as Mathematics, Physics, Biology and Technical Drawing for small groups of high school children. In San Juan, Spain.

#### 2007 - 2007 Store Clerk

Working for Alcampo S.A. restocking and maintaining a section of a supermarket and providing customer service. In Alicante, Spain.

## **LANGUAGES**

Spanish



English



Swedish

### HOBBIES

Painting digitally, listening to music and playing video games are among my favourite indoors activities. When I want to enjoy my time outside I go running or hiking, or I have a nice coffee with good company.